我属下刚刚了解到
My office has just learned
近来与总统交往的女人
that the woman with whom the President is currently involved,
Anne Packard医生正由于
Dr. Ann Packard, is being accused
伪造临床药检结果而被指控
of helping to fabricate the results of a clinical drug trial.
我们处境不乐观
We got hit hard.
骑墙观望的选民很可能转而支持Keeler
Voters who were on the fence may have just fallen into Keeler's camp.
但是一旦他们发现Ted在撒谎 就会知道这是无稽之谈...
Well, that is ridiculous. Once they find out that Ted was lying...
但他们怎么会知道 Anne?
And how are they supposed to do that, Ann?
这一切都是人云亦云 这就是政治
It's he said, she said. See, this is politics.
并不像治病 所以麻烦你别掺和进来
It's not medicine, so do me a favor and stay out of it.
我现在替代Tony 给我最新消息
I'm taking over for Tony. Give me an update.
我们正试图和直升机联系
We're trying to make contact with the chopper.
现在我们已经找到了Kyle Singer 而病毒也被隔离
Now that we have Kyle Singer, and the virus is contained,
我们得联系Jack 让他明白 帮助Salazar逃离已无关紧要
we need to contact Jack, let him know that the attempted escape of Salazar is pointless.
Salazar的恐怖组织对我国造成严重威胁
Salazar's terrorist connections are a serious threat to this country.
Salazar和Bauer都是弃子
Both Salazar and Bauer are expendable.
怎么了Chase?
What's going on, Chase?
你父亲在我联系上他之前就离开了直升机
Your dad got out before I could tell him about Kyle Singer.
现在正和Salazar逃亡中
He and Salazar are on the run.
现在的关键是要让他知道
The only thing that matters right now is getting word to him that
病毒已经被隔离
the virus has been contained.
这样他就会交出Salazar
That way, he'll turn Salazar over.
上次的电话里 你兄弟给了FBI的联系方式
Your brother gave the FBI contact instructions in his last call.
他的飞机正准备接你
He's got a plane circling, waiting to pick you up.
你果然是最棒的 Jack
You really are the best, Jack.
举起双手!
No te muevas, no te muevas! Te mato!
到底怎么回事?
What the hell's going on?
你把我送到这儿来 我还会让你走吗?
You didn't think I was going to let you just deliver me and leave, did you?
Ramon!
Adam!
Adam 这里出事了...
Adam, there's something seriously wro...
我刚想起来
I just remembered,
我没关那个文件夹
I forgot to close that file.
以下事件发生于晚上7点至8点之间
The following takes place between 7:00 am and 8:00 am
- Gael你在做什么? 放开我  - 对不起 Kim
- Gael, what are you doing? Let me go.  - Sorry, Kim.
- 不!  - 你不该扯进来的
- No!  - You shouldn't have walked into this.
冷静点 我只想问你几个问题 好么?
Calm down. I have to ask you a few questions, okay?
这个房间是是隔音的 如果你叫喊
Now, this room is soundproof, so if you scream,
除了惹我发火 别无他用 这不会是你希望的
it won't do anything but make me mad, and you don't want to do that.
这点我们能达成共识吧?
So, we're going to be all right here?
你们对我父亲怎么了?
What are you doing to my father?
我来发问 明白?
I'll ask the questions, huh?
你是来更新登记记录的
You came in here to bring the logs backup to date.
他们估计你多久会完成?
When do they expect you to finish?
我不会问第二遍
Don't make me ask you twice.
我不知道 10分钟
I don't know, ten minutes.
那么之后你的工作是?
And after that, what are you working on?
只是处理杂务
Just utility work.
很好
Good.
你明白你在做什么? 这行不通的
What do you think you're doing? This isn't going to work.
Adam?
- 怎么  - 你听说了没有
- Yeah?  - I don't know if you've gotten word,
Tony的手术已经完成 我准备几分钟后赶过去
but Tony's out of surgery. I'm trying to head over there in a few minutes.
那么你走了后 谁负责?
Well, who's going to be in charge when you're gone?
Gael 我要你将我所有的档案全部转移到他的系统里 明白?
Gael. I want you to unmount all my directories and transfer them over to his system, okay?
好
Sure.
有Jack的新消息么?
Anything new on Jack?
没 已知的最后踪迹是市中心的地铁站
No. Our last location on him was the downtown subway station,
之后Chase就跟丢了
and Chase lost his trail after that.
我们联系洛杉矶警局了么?
Have we contacted LAPD?
对 他们正为此忙着呢 地方FBI也是
Yeah. They're all over it. So is the local FBI.
很好
Great.
我不认为我们应该这样处理
I think we're going about this the wrong way.
Jack帮Salazar越狱 因为他认定唯有这样能阻止生化危机
Jack broke Salazar out of jail because he thought it was the only way to stop the bio threat,
但现在我们已经找到Kyle Singer 危机已解除
but now that we have Kyle Singer, there is no threat.
我们应该透露给媒体 Jack也许能得到消息
We should just saturate the media, and maybe Jack will get the message.
但是总统明确指示
But the President made it very clear.
他现在并不想让大众得知生化危机
He does not want the public to know about the bio threat.
至少不是现在
Not at this point.
我们得独力找到Jack和Salazar
We have to find Jack and Salazar ourselves.
明白
Yeah.
Dessler.
Dessler
Michelle 是我
Michelle, it's me.
Gael 你为什么还不来电讯会议室?
Gael, why aren't you in the teleconference room?
简报马上要开始了
The briefing's about to begin.
Kim碰上了些隐藏的记录文件无法移动
Yeah, well, Kim bumped into some imbedded no-ops in the log files.
这要一会
It'll take a few minutes.
她能解决
She can handle that.
听着 我要尽快赶往医院
Look, I'm trying to head over to the hospital.
我要你快点 这样你可以暂替我
I need you up to speed so you can takeover for me.
我现在过来
I'm on my way.
谢谢
Thank you.
我会看着你
I'm watching you.
因此不要轻举妄动
So don't try anything.
明白?
Alright?
将空袭警报的编码交给Gael
Transfer all blue alert key codes to Gael.
还有么?
Anything else?
没了 谢谢
That's it. Thanks.
洛杉矶已经脱离了病毒扩散危机
There is no longer an outbreak threat for the city of Los Angeles.
被Salazar手下所挟持的Kyle Singer
Kyle Singer, who is being held by Salazar's people,
并没有感染cordelia病毒 而是完全健康
was not carrying the cordelia virus and turns out to be perfectly healthy,
但是我们确信Salazar的组织持有病毒
but we do know Salazar's organization has the virus,
因此寻找Ramon Salazar是首要事项
which means finding Ramon Salazar is our top priority.
感谢前来 Gael
Thank you for joining us, Gael.
如果你准备代替Michelle 准时点
If you're taking over for Michelle, be on time.
抱歉
Sorry.
从现在起 我们将集中精力
I was just saying from this moment on, we are focused on one thing only
追捕Ramon Salazar.
and that's finding Ramon Salazar.
Adam 我们目前进行得怎么样?
Adam, where are we on that?
Jack和Ramon下了直升机后 我们就跟丢了
Um, after Jack and Ramon ditched the chopper, we lost their trail.
- 据我们所知 他们还在洛杉矶  - 他们呆不久
- For all we know, they're still in L.A.  - Well, they won't be for long.
我们怀疑他们正前往Mexico边境
We suspect they're heading for the Mexican border.
我们已经通知Mexico政府和其它的美洲中部各盟友
We've contacted the Mexican government as well as Central American allies.
我们要求他们监视所有空域
We're asking them to monitor all air quarters.
Chase Edmunds呢?
What about Chase Edmunds?
我估计他正在赶回来
I'm assuming that he's coming back here.
别做没有根据的估计
Don't assume anything.
Ramon来口吧
Ramon, have a drink.
你是自由身了
You're a free man.
谢谢
Thank you.
Ramon...
你好 Jack
Hello, Jack.
我想告诉你 宴会举行的很不错
The party's going well. I wanted you to know.
除此以外 还有
There's something else I want you to know.
不知为何 Hector想要留你一命
For some reason, Hector wants you alive.
也许他想要亲手杀了你
Maybe he wants to kill you himself.
也许他想看着我杀你
Or maybe he wants to watch me do it.
我不知道我能不能忍这么久
I'm just not sure I can wait that long.
Ramon
Ramon,
让我们继续宴会吧
Let's get back to the party.
来吧 那些女孩 Sandra等着你呢
Come on, the girls. Sandra is waiting.
- 喂?  - Chase 我是Ryan Chappelle
- Yeah?  - Chase, this is Ryan Chappelle.
你在干吗?
What are you doing?
试图找到Jack
Trying to find Jack.
反恐局的人都在找
So is the rest of CTU.
我可能已经有头绪了
Well, I may have a thread.
说吧
Tell me.
Jack和我曾经收拢过Hector Salazar的线人
Jack and I back pocketed some of Hector Salazar's contacts
都是地下组织的
That aren't on the books.
如果你有消息 我们会让别的行动组了解
If you have any information, we'll pass it on to another field team,
但我现在要你回来
but I want you back here.
Ryan没时间了 只要Jack把Ramon Salazar
Ryan, there's no time for that. As soon as Jack hands Ramon Salazar
交给他兄弟 他们就会杀了他
over to his brother, they're gonna kill him.
- Jack可能已经死了  - 在我获得实据前 我不会停手
- Jack may already be dead.  - Well, I'm not stopping until I know for sure.
Chase
Chase,
我要你立即回来
I want you back here now.
为什么?
Why?
因为我发现Jack在使用海洛因
Because I just found out Jack's been using heroin.
既然你是他的搭档 你一定知道
And since you're his partner, you must have known.
不 我不知道
No, I had no idea.
我不相信
I don't believe you.
我认为你一直帮他隐瞒着
I believe you've been covering for him all along.
长官 现在的关键是找到Jack
Sir, the only thing that matters right now is finding Jack,
呆在反恐局里 什么都干不了
and I can't do that from CTU.
如果你还想要继续干下去
If you even want a chance of keeping your job,
你就得马上回来 并且向我报告Bauer的情况
you'll get back here now and debrief me on Bauer.
明白了么?
Do you understand?
- 明白  - 很好
- Yes, I understand.  - Good.
- O'Brian  - Chloe Kim在上面么?
- O'Brian.  - Chloe, is Kim up there?
- 不在  - 你的登记还是6小时前的吗?
- No.  - Are your logs still lagging by six hours?
让我看下
Let me check.
是的
Yup.
我以为Kim已经更新了
I thought Kim was supposed to take care of that.
我不知道Kim在做什么 我不了解她的安排
I don't know what Kim is doing. I don't follow her schedule that closely.
Gael...
你现在要回维护中心么?
Are you going back to tech one right now?
不 现在不回 怎么了?
No, not right now. Why?
我需要Kim帮忙 没事 我会去找她?
Uh... I just need something from Kim. It's cool. I'll get her.
不 她不在那儿
No, no, she's not there.
她在 她在更新登陆信息
Yes, she is. She's backing up logs.
她之前在 但是Chappelle让她给网络做个镜像
She was, but Chappelle asked her to bring a mirror drive down to networking.
几分钟内她就回来 你想要什么?
She'll be back in a few minutes. What do you need?
我想要什么?
What do I need?
我想要找到Jack
I need to find Jack.
我们四处碰壁 Kim是他的女儿
We're dead ending everywhere. Kim's his daughter.
也许有她能帮我们处理我们忽略的部分
Maybe there's something we're overlooking she can help us with.
只要她一回来 我就让她找你 行么?
As soon as she gets back, I'll send her over, okay?
好吧
Yeah, okay.
Gael 我让Adam将我所有的信息转到了你的系统下面
Gael, I had Adam transfer all my directories over to your system.
- 你已经可以开始了  - 非常感谢
- You're good to go.  - Thanks. Great.
等下
Oh, hold on.
我要看下局里来的快电
I want to go over the dispatches from Division.
一共派出了17组人马
There's 17 units out in the field.
其中5组还在市中心 试图寻找Jack的蛛丝马迹
5 of them are still downtown. They're trying to pick up Jack's trail.
其余的12组呢?
And the other 12?
卫生部 LAX...
Health services, LAX...
等等 让我把剩下的给你
Umm hold on, let me pull up the rest for you.
这是我用来调整人手的表格
This is the matrix I used to balance resources.
我会发给你的
I'll transfer it to you.
Tony的手术已经结束了?
Is Tony out of surgery?
是的
Yeah.
他不会有事吧?
Is he going to be okay?
希望如此
Hope so.
- Dessler  - Michelle Gael和你在一起么?
- Dessler.  - Michelle, is Gael still with you?
- 对 怎么了? - 我进不了维护中心 密码失效了
- Yeah. Why?  - I can't get into tech one. I'm having trouble with the access code.
你把维护中心的密码改了?
Did you change the access codes to tech one?
不 怎么? 出什么问题了?
No. Why? What's going on?
- Adam进不去  - 他进去干嘛?
- Adam can't get in.  - What does he need?
- 你进去干嘛 Adam?  - 我在找Kim 她之前在这儿
- What do you need, Adam?  - I'm looking for Kim and she was in there.
- 你给她打电话了么?  - 电话出故障了
- Did you try calling her?  - There's something wrong with the phone.
你能强制打开门么? 门锁住了
Can you override the door? Cause it's tweaked.
没问题
Yeah, sure.
- 你在干嘛  - 覆盖密码
- What are you doing?  - Overriding the access code.
也许键入板出现问题了
Probably something wrong with the keypad.
好了 我把密码改成 1-2-3-4
Okay, I'm resetting it to 1-2-3-4.
需要15秒时间
It'll take 15 seconds to sync, though.
多谢
Thanks.
我把所有和病毒有关的发到A盘
Okay, I'm sending everything related to the virus over to volume A.
你要Salazar的文件放到哪里?
Where do you want the Salazar file?
Kim?
天呐 Kim!
Oh, my god, Kim!
- Kim?  - Adam 是Gael干的
- Kim?  - Adam, it was Gael.
第5区没发现
Section 5 is clear.
我发现目标
I have a visual of the subject.
在第5区
Section 5.
封锁他的出口!
Block him off on the other side!
下来! 快!
Get down here! Come on!
第七区 我封住了朝东走廊
Section 7. I'm blocking down the east corridor.
我没看见目标
I do not have a visual on the subject.
我重复 我没看见目标
I repeat. I do not have a visual on the subject.
请指示
Please advise.
第7区需要医生
We need a doctor on section 7.
我重复! 朝东走廊!
I repeat! The east corridor!
放下枪!
Put it down, put it down!
别乱动 放下枪
Don't do it. Put it down, now.
Gael!
别拦着我 Michelle!
Don't get in my way, Michelle!
外面的警卫已经各就各位了
External security is already in position.
你走投无路了
You're not going anywhere.
你再越雷池一步 后果自负
You take one step outside, you know exactly what will happen.
好 我会的
Yeah, okay, I will.
谢谢
Thanks.
他们怎么说?
What did they say?
他们还没找到Jack Bauer
They haven't found Jack Bauer yet.
甚至不知道他还在不在城里
Not even sure if he's even still in the city.
他不在城里
He's not in the city.
他的计划是 把Ramon Salazar回他兄弟那里来阻止病毒扩散
His plan was to take Ramon Salazar back to his brother to prevent the outbreak.
这就是他会做的 即使牺牲生命
That's what he's going to do, even if it costs him his life.
David 这没错 但是我们现在对此无能为力
You know, David, that's probably true, but there's nothing we can do about that now.
我们的情报机关和军队正没日没夜的奋斗在前线
Our intelligence and military services are working overtime on that front, so
让他们去处理这事
let them do their job.
我们眼下还有别的麻烦要解决
We, unfortunately, have other fires to put out.
David 我对Ted和这场辩论感到抱歉
David, I'm sorry about Ted and the debate.
别这么说
I don't want to hear it.
你没错
It's not your fault.
是我让你去面对他
I was the one that told you to stand up to him,
也许我错了 也许你应该直接用钱把他打发走
but maybe I was wrong, maybe you should have just paid him off.
你并没有错
You were not wrong.
总统先生...
Mr. President...
我们还有很多要忙
we have a lot of work to do.
我依旧无法相信Gael会是叛徒
I still can't believe Gael could be a traitor.
他说了什么?
Has he said anything?
我们还没开始呢 要先让他紧张
We haven't gone in yet. We're sweating him first.
听着Ryan
Listen, Ryan,
Tony的手术结束了
Tony's out of surgery.
我希望他醒来后能看到我
I want to be there when he wakes up.
而我需要你留在这儿
And I need you here.
我们刚抓到一个卧底
We just uncovered a mole.
我们不知道到底多少机密泄露到Salazar手中
We don't know how badly we've been compromised by Salazar.
有你处理这事就行了
But you're handling that.
如果忙不过来 你可以让Chloe帮忙
Anything that spills over, you can give to Chloe.
Chloe才是麻烦所在
Chloe's a pain in the ass.
她能行
She can do it,
至少在我回来之前
at least until I get back.
好吧 如果你认为可以丢下手头的工作
Fine, if you think you're dispensable.
我只是想陪着我丈夫
I just want to be with my husband.
好吧
All right.
谢谢
Thank you.
让我们开始吧
All right, let's do this.
你忽悠了我们 Gael
You had us, Gael.
现在我们逮住你了
Now we have you.
还有其它Salazar的卧底吗?
Were you working alone, or does Salazar have other moles inside?
你认识Johnson
You know Johnson.
你知道Johnson是干什么的
You know what Johnson does.
你也知道 迟早 你会把你知道的告诉我
And you know that sooner or later, you're going to tell me what you know.
问题是 你想要什么样的过程
The only question is how hard you make this on yourself.
Kim说你在监视Jack Bauer登上的飞机
Kim says you were monitoring a plane that had Jack Bauer on it.
真的么?
Is that true?
我无可奉告
I have nothing to say.
如果这是你在被揭露前 做的最后一件事
If it's the last thing you ever do,
你就得告诉我 那飞机要降落在哪里
you're going to tell me where that plane is landing.
怎么了Ramon?
What is it, Ramon?
你不喜欢这些美女?
Don't you like the girls?
告诉我为什么 为什么Hector要留Bauer一条命
Tell me again why Hector wants Bauer alive.
我不知道 他没有解释
I don't know. He didn't say, but...
但是...
But...
没为什么
but nothing.
我和Bauer不共戴天
Every Time Bauer takes a breath, he's an insult to me.
因为他的背叛 我坐了3个月的牢
I spent three months in prison because of his betrayal.
我知道Ramon 我确信Hector也这么想
I know, Ramon, and I'm sure that Hector feels the same way.
那他不会介意
Then he won't mind.
Ramon别!
Ramon, no!
你在命令我么 Tomas?
Are you giving me an order, Tomas?
Ramon
Ramon,
我为你们兄弟俩工作
I work for you and your brother.
我对你们敬爱有加
I love and respect both of you.
Hector命令我把Bauer活着带下飞机
Hector instructed me to keep Bauer alive until the plane lands.
而我命令你坐下
And I'm instructing you to sit down.
你为什么不尊重你兄弟的意见?
Why won't you honor the one wish of your brother,
他一心谋划了你的潜逃
who arranged for your escape today?
在一小时之内
In less than an hour,
我保证你一定能报复Bauer
I am sure that you will get your revenge on Bauer.
我们走着瞧
We'll see.
给我再倒一杯
Pour me another drink.
是 Ramon
Yes, Ramon.
Pedro
Pedro.
我不该和你说话 Jack
I'm not supposed to talk to you, Jack.
好吧 那听着
Fine, then listen.
我拚着命将Ramon救出来
I risked my life getting Ramon out of prison.
也是你把他送进去的
You put him in prison.
Pedro 我有要事得告诉Ramon
Pedro, I need to tell Ramon something it's important
在他喝的酩酊大醉之前 你见过那样子
before he gets too wasted. You know what he's like.
是啊 有次他喝醉了 把某人扔下飞机
Yeah. Got drunk one time threw some guy off a plane.
如果这次也一样
Keeps going like this,
你可能会比我们先着陆
you might be landing before we do.
- 看在上帝的份上 听我说一句  - 不 你听我说
- For god's sakes, listen to me.  - No, you listen to me.
我没话和你说
I'm not talking to you.
你已经死到临头了
You're a dead man.
Jack
Jack.
Jack 别装腔了
Jack, quit screwing around, Jack. Jack.
最坏情况下 我们能以国防问题来解释你的离场
Bottom line is, I think we can explain the national security issue that pulled you off stage,
但是针对Ann的指控很难解决
but the allegation against Ann is going to be a lot harder to handle.
他的前夫肯定有自己的目的
Her ex-husband clearly had his own agenda.
要证明他是个骗子应该不难
And it shouldn't be difficult to prove that he's a liar.
我明白 大众很期待去了解其中的黑幕
I understand that, but this is dirty laundry, and we both know the public wants to hear it,
但如果你拿不出实证 Ann就会拖累你
and unless you can offer the public something definitive Ann is going to hurt you.
Jerry说得对
Jerry's right.
David 我作为你兄弟和顾问 我有些建议
Listen, David. I'm your brother, I'm your advisor and I do have some perspective on this thing.
你想听听看么?
Now, do you want to hear it?
好 说吧
Yes, I want to hear it.
- 和Ann保持距离  - Wayne...
- Distance yourself from Ann.  - Oh, Wayne...
先让我说完 再让我闭嘴
Before you shut me down, just hear me out.
由于Sherry 你已经人心尽失了
You used up the public's goodwill with Sherry.
他们不想知道你还和某些
They don't want to hear about you being involved with someone else
不值得信任的人相处
who's not trustworthy.
你得尊重你的选民
You have got to respect the people who voted for you.
对不起
Oh, excuse me.
喂?
Hello?
Ann 是我 Ted
Ann, it's me, Ted.
我们得聊一聊
We need to talk.
聊什么?
About what?
你还有什么能和我说的?
What could you possibly have to say to me?
以你所做的一切 我无法相信你居然还敢打来
After what you have done, I can't believe you have the audacity to call.
- 我很抱歉  - 好极了
- I'm sorry.  - Well, that's great.
你让事情变得好极了
Now everything's all right.
我因此才联系你 我希望弥补自己造成的损害
That's why I called. Because I want to make it right.
怎么做?
How?
你以为能挽回所做的一切?
How can you possibly undo the damage you've done?
来我办公室见我 我会解释一切
Come up in my office. Come up and I'll explain everything.
我不会去的
I'm not coming over there.
Ann 听我说
Ann, listen to me.
我有文件能够证明你清白
I have some documents that will prove your innocence.
什么文件?
What kind of documents?
信和备忘录
Letters and memos.
行么?
Please?
我只是想亲自交给你
This is how I want to do it. I want to give them to you personally.
我保证不会耍花样
I promise I won't make a scene.
- 我会让别人去拿的  - 不行!
- I'll send someone over to get them.  - No!
以我的方法办 不然我现在就把证据烧了
Now, we agree it's my way, or I swear I'll burn them right now.
好吧 希望你最好不要浪费我的时间
All right, but you'd better not be wasting my time.
Simon
Simon,
- 我们得谈谈  - Chase Edmunds
- we need to talk.  - Chase Edmunds.
很抱歉 我正在吃晚饭
Sorry, but I'm having dinner right now.
- 你想要什么?  - 我要消息!
- What do you want?  - I want information!
- 你疯了么?!  - 怎么了?
- Are you crazy?!  - What's going on?
Rita 把孩子带上楼
Rita, take the kids upstairs.
不会有事的
Everything will be fine.
你要查什么?
What do you want?
Ramon Salazar今天越狱了
Ramon Salazar broke out of federal prison today.
他会和他兄弟Hector会合
He's gonna hook up with his brother, Hector.
我告诉过你和Bauer 我是遵纪守法的会计师!
I told you and your partner Bauer that I'm a legitimate accountant!
我和Salazar兄弟没关系
I don't have any business dealings with the Salazars.
Simon我不是来抓你的
Simon, I did not come here to bust you.
但找不到Hector 我是不会走的
And I am not leaving until I know where Hector is.
你明白么?
Do you understand me?
我不知道Hector在哪儿
I don't know where Hector is now.
他两星期前离开了哥伦比亚
He left Colombia over two weeks ago.
他没有告诉你目的地?
And he didn't tell you where he was going?
没有
No.
你不是有他账户信息么?
You're tied into his money flow, right?
对
Yes.
有些
Some of it.
让我们看看
Let's take a look.
Ramon
Ramon,
Hector马上就要和我们见面了 再等几分钟
Hector is meeting us. Just wait a few minutes.
Ramon 拜托了 Hector说...
Ramon, please. Hector said...
你准备好受死了么 Jack?
Are you ready to die, Jack?
退后!
Back up!
退后 不然我就杀了他!
Get back or I'll kill him!
- 退后!  - 开枪 Thomas!
- Get back!  - Shoot him, Thomas!
开枪!
Shoot him!
我死了 他也活不成
If I die, he dies.
难道你要Hector看到这结果?
Is that what you want Hector to see when you get off this plane?
放下武器!
Drop the weapons!
Bajen.
Bajen
Jack 你已经走投无路了
Jack, there's no way out of this for you.
他说得对 我兄弟外面有一群部队
He's right. My brother has an army out there.
我们现在已经不在你老巢了 Jack
We're not in your backyard anymore, Jack.
这事我来担心 你只管坐下
I'll worry about that. You just take a seat.
美女们 别怕
Hey, ladies, don't worry.
一切都在掌握之中
Everything's under control.
等到着陆后 我们继续狂欢
The party will continue once we're on the ground.
伟大的美国英雄
The big American hero.
你觉得呢 Jack?
And what do you think, Jack?
Hector不也正等着你?
That Hector is not prepared for you, huh?
闭嘴
Shut up.
搞定了? 好
Lo tienes? Okay.
过来! 快!
Ven aca! Rapido, rapido!
快上车!
Come on! Get in the car!
为什么你需要那么人去接你兄弟?
Why do you need so many people to pick up your brother?
我想在飞机着陆前做好准备
I want to be prepared when the plane lands.
- 准备什么?  - 任何情况
- Prepared for what?  - Whatever.
我联系不上Gael
I haven't heard from Gael.
他本来该联系的
He should have checked in by now.
- 那么 为什么你不联系Ramon的飞机?  - 太危险了
- So why don't you call Ramon's plane?  - It's too risky.
美国人正在遍地搜索
The Americans are checking everything.
再拿些武器! 快!
Mas! Armas! Come on! Rapido!
快!
Come on!
我得走了?
I have to go, okay?
快走!
Rapido! Come on.
你还有其他同伙么 Gael?
Who else is working with you, Gael?
我明说吧
Let me make something clear.
我很乐意看到 你以叛徒的身份被吊起来
I would love nothing more than to hang you as a traitor
并挣扎至死
and watch you jerk till you're dead.
但我也是现实主义者
But I'm a realist.
如果你能招供 也许我们会放你一马
If there are others, tell me now and we might be able to cut you a deal.
是Hector打来的?
Is that Hector?
Adam 给我拿个跟踪器过来
Adam, bring me a tracking node now.
快! Hector Salazar正在打电话
Now! Hector Salazar's calling.
Kim 把手提电脑拿过来
Kim, grab that laptop.
- 接C5口 Kim  - 明白
- Put the socket in C5, Kim.  - Got it.
快
Hurry up.
开始
Okay, go.
敢说错一个字 我保证让你追悔莫及
One wrong word, I swear to god, I'll make you regret it.
- 喂  - 你在干吗呢?
- Hello.  - Where have you been?
我很忙 没空联系你
Busy. I don't have a lot of time.
Ramon在哪儿?
Where is Ramon?
在回去的路上
On his way to you.
他安全么?
Is he safe?
应该是
Think so.
Bauer呢?
What about Bauer?
- 不知道  - 什么叫不知道?!
- Don't know.  - What do you mean you don't know, huh?!
你在做什么呢?
What are doing there?
他们让我去忙别的了
They put me on something else.
看的太紧 无法抽身
They're watching me.
有情况联系我
Call me when you have something.
明白
Yeah.
查到了么?
Did we get it?
没有
No.
见鬼
Damn it.
你在忙什么?
How you doing?
你让我担心死了
You scared the hell out of me.
我知道 对不起
I know. I'm sorry.
医生 他怎么样?
How's he doing, doctor?
这是预期的最好结果
We couldn't have hoped for better results.
几天内他就能下床
He should be on his feet in a few days.
他什么时候能出院?
When can he come home?
明天大概就行
Probably tomorrow.
我只是想看着他 确保病情稳定
I just want to keep an eye on him. Make sure he stays stable.
医生
Listen, uh, doctor.
能让我们单独呆会么?
Could we have a couple minutes, please?
- 当然  - 谢谢
- Of course.  - Thanks.
Michelle.
Michelle
怎么?
Yeah?
总统把Salazar放出来了么?
Did the President let Salazar out of prison?
不 是Jack帮他脱狱的
No. No, Jack broke him out.
我们认为他这么做 是为了不让总统为难
We think he did it so the President wouldn't have to make the hard choice.
- 他逃走了么?  - 对
- Did he get away?  - Yeah.
我得立即和Gael联系
I have to talk to Gael right away.
怎么?
What?
- Gael?  - 对
- Gael?  - Yeah.
怎么 他出事了?
What, something happen to him?
Tony Gael是Salazar兄弟的人
Tony, Gael's been working for the Salazars.
你如何得知的?
How do you know that?
他在技术1部 监控Salazar脱逃
He was using tech one to monitor Salazar's escape.
当我们发现后 他试图逃跑
And then when we found out, he tried to run.
他目前在哪儿?
Where is he now?
他还在反恐局
He's still at CTU.
Chappelle和Johnson正在审问他
Chappelle and Johnson are questioning him.
不行 亲爱的 你去哪儿?
No, honey, where are you going?
你现在就得带我过去
You have to get me over there right now.
不 你哪儿也不能去
No, you're not going anywhere.
医生!
Doctor, doctor!
Doctor!
Almeida先生 你在干什么?
Mr. Almeida, what are you doing?
听着 我现在得走?
Look, I have to get out of here, all right?
你可以把我转交给反恐局的医疗部
You can release me to CTU medical if you want.
我不能这么做
I can't do that.
听着!
All right, look, look!
如果你担心责任问题 我妻子会在出院文件上签字
If you're worried about liability, my wife will sign me out.
听着 Michelle
Look, Michelle,
现在我需要你信任我
if I ever needed you to trust me, it's now.
看 这是他在波哥大的转账纪录
You see, these are the bank transfers that he made from his account in Bogota.
两星期前停止了运作
They stopped two weeks ago.
查那些钱
Follow the money.
被转移到哪儿?
Where did it go?
有一部分转到了洛杉矶
Some of it to a bank account here in L.A.
一个叫David Gomez的人的帐上
A David Gomez.
这我们知道 别的呢?
Yeah, we already know about that. What else?
- 有意思  - 怎么?
- That's interesting.  - What?
72万美元 转给了一个
$720,000 deposited.
我从来没见过的账户
I've never seen this account.
哪里?
Where is it?
Banco del Oeste.
Banco del Oeste
是在墨西哥的一个小镇
It's in a town in Mexico.
- Las Nieves  - 让我看下
- Las Nieves.  - Okay, look out.
肯定是这儿了
That's got to be it.
好极了
Good.
我们弄完了么?
We're done?
- 不完全  - 还有什么?
- Not quite.  - What else?
你有私人飞机吧?
You have a private plane, don't you?
对
Yes.
准备让它起飞
Clear it for takeoff.
嗨 Kim
Hey, Kim.
嗨 Chloe
Hey, Chloe.
他伤到你了?
Did he hurt you?
我指 Gael
Gael, I mean.
不
No.
这太疯狂了 他在我们这儿干了2年 在情报局干了5年
It's crazy. I mean, he's been here, what, two years and the CIA, five before that
像他这种人怎么会是恐怖分子?
how does someone like that end up a terrorist?
我也不知道 Chloe
I don't know, Chloe.
听着
Listen...
我只是想告诉你 我从来不认为你父亲是坏人
I want to tell you that I don't think your dad's a bad person.
如果我有什么冒犯你的地方 我对此道歉
If I ever said anything to offend you, I'm sorry.
没关系 谢谢
It's okay. Thanks.
好 我终于说出来了
There, I've said it.
- 喂?  - Kim是我 没人在旁边吧?
- Hello?  - Kim, it's me. Are you alone?
等下
Hold on.
你在哪儿? Chappelle要你回来
Where are you? Chappelle ordered you back here.
没错 但听着
Yeah, he did, but listen.
在我找到你父亲前 我不会回来
I'm not coming back until I find your father.
你准备怎么做?
How are you gonna do that?
我刚找到Hector Salazar的位置
I just found out where Hector Salazar is.
墨西哥北部Las Nieves小镇
Small town in northern Mexico Calledlas Nieves.
我相信Jack带Ramon正前往那里
I'm sure Jack's taking Ramon there now.
不 Chase 事情正相反
No, Chase, it's the other way around.
- 是Ramon把我父亲带走了  - 你怎么知道?
- Ramon's taking my dad.  - How do you know that?
有监视录像记录了
There was a video feed...
我亲眼看见的
and I saw it.
他们敲晕了我爸爸 并把他拖上了飞机
They knocked my dad out and dragged him onto a plane.
等等 监视录像 Kim? 我听不懂
Well, wait, wait a minute. A video feed, Kim? I don't understand.
Gael 一直在为Salazar兄弟工作
Gael, has been working for the Salazars.
他一直看着全程
He's been watching everything through
Gael?
没错 Gael一直在帮Salazar兄弟做事
Yes, Gael has been helping the Salazars this whole time.
Gael有说什么?
Was Gael talking?
我不知道
I don't know.
Chappelle正在审他
Chappelle's got him now,
我不知道是否审出了什么
but I don't know if they're getting anywhere.
我没有收到任何消息
I haven't heard anything.
Kim 反恐局已经被泄密了 别让人知道我们通过电话
Okay, Kim, CTU has been compromised. You cannot tell anyone you've talked to me, okay?
- 那么Chappelle呢?  - 特别是他
- What about Chappelle?  - Especially not Chappelle.
你不能孤身前往
You cannot go in there alone.
Hector有一批人马等着
Hector's gonna have an army down there.
有必要时我会呼叫支援的
No, I will call for backup when the time's right.
我要你保证 你不会让任何人知道我们的谈话
I need to hear you promise, you're not gonna tell anyone you talked to me.
我不知道 Chase
I don't know, Chase.
好好想想 相信我 Kim
Think about it. Don't do this to us, Kim.
- 这太冒险  - 我不是不相信你
- There's too much at stake.  - I'm not doing anything to us.
这事关你
This is about your life
和我父亲的生命
and my dad's.
听着 我知道这有多重要 见鬼
Look, I know what this is about, damn it.
好好听着 我得潜入
Just listen to me. I have to go dark.
没时间争执 必须马上去
There's no time to argue about it. Just do this.
Kim.
Kim
多保重 Chase
Be careful, Chase.
Kim.
Kim
Kim!
说吧 硬汉 你打算怎么着?
So, tell me, tough guy, what's the plan?
你迟早会知道
You'll know soon enough.
得了吧 我们都好奇着呢 和姑娘们说说
Come on, we're interested. Tell the girls.
你想等飞机降落后 逮捕Hector
So you think you're going to land the plane and arrest Hector.
不可能 即使是伟大的Jack Bauer 也无法孤身干掉50个人
No. Even the great Jack Bauer can't take 50 men by himself.
我明白了
Oh, I got it.
你准备把我扔下飞机
You're gonna drop me off,
开着飞机就跑
turn the plane around.
等下
Hey, but wait.
你已经是美国的通缉犯了 你准备去哪儿?
You are a criminal in America. Wanted. So where will you go?
我不觉得第三世界国家会欢迎你
I don't think a third-world country will suit you.
这就叫进退两难 Jack
I think that's called a dilemma, Jack.
闭嘴
Shut up.
Adam...
Chappelle在哪儿?
Where's Chappelle?
他和Gael在一起
He's with Gael.
哪儿?
Where?
820审讯室
Interrogation 820.
走吧
Let's go.
出了什么事?
What the hell's going on?
我不知道
I don't know.
告诉我 你个狗娘养的
Talk to me, you son of a bitch.
关门
Get the door.
Johnson 够了
Johnson, that's enough.
- Almeida 你来干嘛?  - 让他出去
- Almeida, what are you doing here?  - Get him out of the room.
为什么?
Why?
相信我 Ryan 让他出去
Trust me, Ryan. Get him out of the room.
你也出去 Ryan
You, too, Ryan.
什么?
What?
让我和Gael单独谈 相信我没错
I got to talk to Gael by myself, all right? Just trust me on this one.
Michelle 到底怎么回事?
Michelle, what's going on?
我不在乎你们之间怎么回事
Look, I don't care what's going on between you two.
我不会离开这间房间
I'm not going anywhere. I'm staying right here.
Ramon?!
Ramon人呢?
Where is Ramon?
我兄弟人呢?!
Where's my brother?!
打死Bauer
Kill him. Kill Bauer.
听到了么?
Do you hear me?
你在干吗 Jack?
What are you doing, Jack?
你兄弟想在飞机上杀了我!
Your brother tried to kill me on the plane!
为什么到处都是你的人?! 这和我们谈好的不一样!
Why all the guns?! This is not what we talked about.
放下武器!
Ibajen sus armas!
我担心死了 Gael也不知道你是否在飞机上
I was worried. Gael wasn't sure you were on the plane.
到你兄弟那儿去
Go see your brother.
兄弟 很高兴见到你
Hi, brother. I'm so glad to see you.
到底怎么回事? 我不明白
What's going on? I don't understand.
我保证马上给你解释
I'll tell you all about it in a minute. I promise.
干得不错 Jack
Good job, Jack.
来吧
Come.
我们还有很多活要忙
We have a lot of work to do.
你在干吗 Hector?
What are you doing, Hector?
来吧
Come.
我会解释的
I'll explain everything.
- 他潜进去了  - 你们在说什么?
- He's in.  - What are you talking about?
- 谁潜进去了?  - Jack
- Who's in?  - Jack.
- 什么?!  - Gael和我一直在为Jack工作
- What?!  - Gael and I have been working with Jack.
我们试图让他潜回Salazar兄弟的组织
We've been trying to get him back undercover with the Salazars.
这个信号说明他已经成功了
That signal means he's back in.
我不明白
I don't understand.
我会解释的 现在我们得联系总统
I'll explain everything. Right now we got to call the President.